https://www.glasgowwestend.co.uk/about/privacypolicy.php

Privacy Policy and Cookie Information
This privacy policy sets out how Pat’s Guide to Glasgow West End uses and protects any information that you give Pat’s Guide to Glasgow West End when you use this website.
It explains how we comply with the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), the DPA (Data Protection Act) [pre GDPR enforcement] and the PECR (Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations).
This policy will explain areas of this website that may affect your privacy and personal details, how we process, collect, manage and store those details and how your rights under the GDPR, DPA & PECR are adhere to.
Additionally it will explain the use of cookies or software, advertising or commercial sponsorship from third parties and the download of any documents, files or software made available to you (if any) on this website. Further explanations may be provided for specific pages or features of this website in order to help you understand how we, this website and its third parties (if any) interact with you and your computer / device in order to serve it to you. Our contact information is provided if you have any questions.
The DPA & GDPR May 2018
We and this website complies to the DPA (Data Protection Act 1998) and already complies to the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) which comes into affect from May 2018. We will update this policy accordingly after the completion of the UK’s exit from the European Union.
Pat’s Guide to Glasgow West End is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Pat’s Guide to Glasgow West End may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 2012.
Glasgow West End: Jim’s Free Photographs: Terms and Conditions
You can take any image from my photograph diary for your own use as long as you are using it on a non-commercial Web site, give me the credit as the photographer (James Byrne) and create a link to the home page of this Web site. If these condition are not met you are not allowed to use any of the images that are on this website and that are the copyright of James Byrne (also called Jim Byrne)
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
your name and email address
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to send you the newsletter you registered for.
Within the newsletter we may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use cookies in the following way:
Traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Cookies set by Google and other advertisers to display relevant adverts on pages of Pat’s Guide to Glasgow West End.
Cookies set when using the Glasgow West End Forum to track discussion and Forum membership.
Cookies set by service providers such as the weather report badget, Twitter Tweet button and Facbook badges.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on this website it will only be used for the purpose stated on the form or for getting in touch with you for reasons related to Pat’s Guide to Glasgow West End.
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [email address]
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. Within our newsletter there may be you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Pat Byrnre, 4/2 1 Ascot Gate, Glasgow, G12 0AP.
There is a link at the foot of all newsletters to allow you to delete yourself form the mailing list if you no longer wish to receive the newsletter.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Resources & Further Information
Overview of the GDPR – General Data Protection Regulation
Data Protection Act 1998
Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003
The Guide to the PECR 2003
Twitter Privacy Policy
Facebook Privacy Policy
Google Privacy Policy
Linkedin Privacy Policy
Mailchimp Privacy Policy
HR Form Templates
Website Privacy Policy Template
Last edited on May 2018 by Jim Byrne of Pat’s Guice to Glasgow West End
This section: About
Filed under: About
Prevous page or post
| Next page or post
Written by : Jim Byrne
West End based web Developer,
writer, songwriter and musician. And the person who takes lots of photos for the Glasgow West End website.
Comments are closed.
Categories
About (3)
Accommodation (10)
American Restaurants (3)
Architecture (8)
archived (1)
Art & artists Glasgow West End (129)
Art, Photography, Exhibitions what's on-glasgow (571)
Astrology Blog by Anne Whitaker (8)
Aye Write 2020 (13)
Aye Write Book Festival 2017 (31)
Aye Write Book Festival 2019 (45)
Aye Write Glasgow's Book Festival 2017 (31)
Aye Write! Book Festival 2018 (31)
Aye Write! Glasgow's Book Festival 2014 (32)
Aye Write! Glasgow's Book Festival 2015 (30)
Aye Write! Glasgow's Book Festival 2016 (42)
Bar Stool Philosopher (11)
Beauty (2)
Beer Gardens Patio Dining (1)
Best In The West (30)
Black History Month Glasgow (14)
Blog: Balloch Open Mic (2)
Bob Law: photographer, walker and writer (44)
Book and Event Reviews (34)
Books, Talks, Poetry and Creative Writing Events (1,837)
Burns Day Celebrations 2017 (6)
Burns Events (48)
Burns Night Glasgow 2015 (12)
Business Directory (7)
Business services (3)
Byres Road New Developments (2)
Cafes and Bistros (22)
Calum Maclean – poet and aspiring writer (27)
Cards and Home Accessories (7)
Celtic Connections 2014 (14)
Celtic Connections 2015 (10)
Celtic Connections 2016 (17)
Celtic Connections 2017 (15)
Celtic Connections 2018 Glasgow's winter music festival (12)
Celtic Connections 2019 (9)
Celtic Connections 2020 (20)
Celtic Connections 2021 (1)
Centre for Open Studies, University of Glasgow (48)
Chris Del Balso's Travel Blog (3)
Christina Byrne (6)
Christmas & Hogmanay Dining Glasgow (12)
Christmas in Glasgow (333)
Christmas in Glasgow 2016 – festive menus, shows, shopping. (66)
Christmas Menus 2018 (9)
Christmas Menus Glasgow 2016 (4)
Christmas Menus Glasgow 2017 (8)
Christmas Menus Glasgow Restaurants 2013 (5)
Christmas Menus Glasgow West End 2015 (6)
Christmas Poems , Stories and Winter Tales (44)
Christmas Shopping in Glasgow (78)
Cinema (2,801)
Clare's West End Business Blog (1)
Classes and Workshops (156)
Clubs (3)
Clubs in Glasgow (3)
Comment (1)
Community event (110)
Community Groups and Charities (11)
Coronavirus (118)
Coronavirus stories and poems (5)
Courses (36)
Dance (124)
David Howat's Glasgow Property Blog: Sales in the City (1)
Delicatessans (3)
Designer Jewellery Glasgow (3)
Dougie Baird Travel Writers Blog (2)
Dresses for special occasions (1)
Eating and drinking Glasgow West End (232)
Eco friendly (2)
Edinburgh Book Festival (14)
European Restaurants (4)
Events, Fairs, Festivals and Fundraisers (1,869)
Eyecare (2)
Festival 2018 (6)
Film reviews (5)
Film Reviews (4)
Film Reviews by Calum Maclean (17)
Fiona Alderman blogging from The Salignac Foundation France (87)
Fionnuala Boyle, blogging about culture, arts and other stuff (11)
Firework Displays Glasgow (9)
Fireworks Displays in Glasgow 2015 (9)
Flat for sale (1)
Food banks (7)
Free Events (36)
French Restaurants (2)
G20 Festival (4)
Galleries (38)
Gallery (4)
Get Fit with Personal Trainer Paul Rutherford (5)
Gifts (13)
Gig Guide plus Club Events (1,317)
Glasgow Botanic Gardens Bicentenary 1817 – 2017 (6)
Glasgow Commonwealth Games 2014 (31)
Glasgow Doors Open Day (6)
Glasgow Film Festival 2014 (20)
Glasgow Film Festival 2015 (26)
Glasgow Film Festival 2016 (27)
Glasgow Film Festival 2017 (26)
Glasgow Film Festival 2017 (9)
Glasgow Film Festival 2018 (21)
Glasgow Film Festival 2019 (30)
Glasgow Film Festival 2020 (36)
Glasgow Hogmanay (12)
Glasgow International (3)
Glasgow international (6)
Glasgow International (3)
Glasgow International 2016 (14)
Glasgow International Comedy Festival (7)
Glasgow International Comedy Festival 2014 (8)
Glasgow International Comedy Festival 2017 (7)
Glasgow international Comedy Festival 2018 (2)
Glasgow International Festival April 2014 (14)
Glasgow Jazz Festival (3)
Glasgow LGBT (9)
Glasgow Science Festival (14)
Glasgow St Patrick's Day 2015 (8)
Glasgow West End Local characters (15)
gorbals (2)
Gordon McCracken (Made In Maryhill) Photographs of Glasgow (2)
Guide (8)
Hallowe'en in Glasgow (102)
Halloween in Glasgow 2015 (15)
Halloween in Glasgow 2016 (16)
Health and Fitness (15)
Helen Rose Hillwalking Diary (80)
Helen St. Helen (5)
Hogmanay Glasgow (10)
Ian Mitchell (10)
Indian Restaurants (21)
interior design (14)
International Restaurants (2)
International Womens Day (12)
International Womens Day 2017 (6)
International Womens Day Glasgow 2015 (4)
Italian Restaurants (14)
James Christie Blog (17)
Jane Sweeney: Blogging about Glasgow and its hidden gems. (4)
Jill Creighton's Blog: A Wry Guide to (Mid)Life (4)
Jim and Pat's West End Chat (2)
Jim Byrne's forgotten life (3)
Jim's Acoustic Music Blog (16)
Jim's West End Photography Diary (74)
Joiners Corner (31)
Kids and young people (450)
Kilimanjaro Climb for Marie Curie (6)
Leela Soma writing and blogging (20)
LGBT Glasgow (50)
LGBT History Month (8)
Local Businesses Glasgow: Latest Deals, Offers and Discounts (2)
Local Projects (3)
Lola Rose: aspiring writer (8)
Love Poems, Stories and Tales from Glasgow writers (31)
Maggie Graham's Page (3)
Markets (10)
Mary Irvine: Writer and Philhellene (133)
maryhill (2)
Maryhill and Possilpark Citizens Advice Bureau (2)
Memoir (2)
Menus (6)
Merchant City Festival (23)
Merchant City Festival 2014 (18)
Merchant City Festival 2015 (8)
Mexican Restaurants (2)
Mother's Day Gifts (12)
Mothers' Day (13)
Muriel Spark Centenary Celebrations (3)
Music (11)
Music Reviews (26)
New Books by Scottish Writers (16)
North Kelvin Meadow and Children's Wood, Glasgow (36)
Online Marketing (2)
Online Shopping (2)
Opticians (1)
Pamela Banchetti (3)
Pantos and Christmas Shows in Glasgow (68)
Pantos and Christmas Shows in Glasgow 2016 (19)
Partick Folk Club (3)
Pat's Home Page Blog (396)
Pauline Keightley (42)
People: Local Glasgow West End Characters (43)
Photography (34)
Podcast: JIm and Pat's West End Chat (5)
Poems and Stories for Autumn (5)
Poetry (28)
Property (1)
Pub Quiz Nights (2)
Rabbie Burns Day Events in Glasgow 2014 (9)
Rachelle Atalla: Film Reviews (2)
Rae McGreevy Fundraising for MYLOL (3)
Recruitment (1)
Refugee Festival Scotland (2)
Rotten English Podcast (3)
Russian (1)
Sara McQueen: blogging about Glasgow (1)
Scenes from Highland Life (3)
Scottih Book Week Glasgow Events 2016 (9)
Scottish Restaurants (15)
Sean's trip to glasgow (1)
Seasonal Stories and Poems by Glasgow Writers (19)
Shipbuilding on the Clyde (1)
Shoes (1)
Shopping (127)
Situations Vacant Glasgow West Ebd (1)
Situations Vacant Glasgow West End (6)
Southside Festival 2015 (4)
Southside Festival Fringe 2016 (11)
Southside Film Festival (31)
Southside Film Festival 2013 (2)
Southside Fringe (2)
Southside Fringe 2014 (5)
Southside Fringe Festival 2015 (3)
Sport, Walks, Cycling in Glasgow (103)
Star Folk Club (32)
Starchild (25)
Stephen Watt, Poet. (15)
stories and poems (51)
Street Food Glasgow (3)
Stuart Paterson: Writer's Blog (5)
Sweet or sharp summer stories and poems (6)
Takeaway (2)
Ten Writers Telling Lies (13)
The Lucky Break Clydebank (5)
The Referendum and Scottish Politics (7)
The Scottish Mental Health Arts and Film Festival (1)
Travel (40)
Trip to Paris (1)
Uncategorized (1)
Unusual West End Facts (1)
upcycling (2)
Valentina Galdi Words Unsaid (4)
Valentine's Day Glasgow 2016 (25)
Valentine's Day Glasgow Gifts (4)
Valentine's Day in Glasgow 2014 (11)
Valentine's Day in Glasgow 2017 (16)
Valentines Day Glasgow (22)
video (1)
Vintage and Retro Clothing (10)
Walks (13)
Walks in Glasgow (6)
Weddings (29)
Weddings Glasgow (30)
West End Festival 2014 (59)
West End Festival 2015 (39)
West End Festival 2016 (49)
West End Festival 2017 (40)
West End Festival Glasgow (106)
West End Miscellany (1)
What's On Glasgow West End: cinema, clubs, theatre, music, events, festivals, community and more (3,362)
What's on Glasgow: Students (61)
What's on in Glasgow: Theatre and Comedy (627)
Winter 2014 (2)
Womens Clothes sand accessories (4)
Womens clothing (1)
Woodlands Community Garden (94)
writers (48)
Writing (87)
Writing for the Festive Season (17)
Writing for the Festive Season 2015 (5)
Wullie Davidson: Blogging about Bus Pass Jaunts in Scotland (5)
Zoom and online events (160)
Register for Pat's newsletter
Click here to register
Sorry, No images found
Gallery Bank Plugin Powered by Tech Banker
Sorry, No images found
Gallery Bank Plugin Powered by Tech Banker
Copyright Glasgow Westend 2009 thru 2017
Contact Pat's Guide to Glasgow West End | About Pat Byrne | Privacy Policy | Design by Jim Byrne Website Design
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
